Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No animals were hurt during the filming
of this series.
I hope my child borns in good health
so that...
...I can see him wearing these.
I hope, Bala Hatun.
I hope.
Give it to me.
Are you all right, Bala Hatun?
I am fine, Zehra.
It is kicking often these days.
It will go away now.
There is more time.
Bala Hatun!
Zehra, my baby is coming!
Lay down a little bit!
Mother told me there was time!
Go tell her! Run!
My child!
Aren't you ashamed at all?
Why are you torturing the children?
But Selcen Mother, they didn't complete
their jobs, twice.
I see how they work and how you work
either.
This was the last!
What do you want from these girls?
Why are you breaking their hearts
instead of mothering them?
What about you?
Kayı's hatuns!
Why aren't you protecting these girls?
Who keeps silent against oppression is
as bad as the one who oppresses.
Does this suit you?
Selcen Mother, Bala Hatun!
What happened to Bala?
Her water broke down, Selcen Mother!
The baby is coming!
Come on, hatuns!
Come on!
Cloth and hot water!
My Osman's child is coming!
Let's go!
How fast you grew up, right?
Oh, my Orhan!
I both want to see you become a valiant...
...and wonder how you will be when you
grow up.
But I also want you to never grew up and
be in my arms forever.
But don't listen to me, my Orhan.
You surely will grow up, my valiant son!
The foal grows, the horse rests...
...the son grows, the father rests.
My heart!
Can I come in, Malhun?
Come in, Aygül!
What is it, Aygül?
It's good news.
Bala...
...the birth started.
Our Orhan will have a sibling!
What are you saying, Aygül?
Selcen Mother said there was more time.
What if it is just a cramp?
We were surprised too but...
...her water broke down.
My mother is with her, don't worry.
May it come with blessings.
I hope.
May my Orhan's sibling be
born in good health.
I hope. I hope.
Come on, let's go!
Inform Ayşe Hatun too.
I will.
Come on.
My Orhan...
...let's see if your sibling is a girl
or a boy.
My child!
-My girl!
-Mother!
Mother, my baby is coming!
-Thankfully!
-My baby is coming!
Our child is coming!
Zehra, put a pillow behind her!
Come on!
Thank you, my Allah!
Come here. Let's open this.
Tell me, does your pain come often?
Yes, mother!
It hurts terribly, mother!
It will pass, my girl.
When you hold your child in your
arms, all your pain will end.
I hope!
Mother, what is the situation?
Her pain comes and goes.
I hope it will come in health.
Come on, Bala!
Hang in there!
Zehra, come on!
Hot water, clothes!
Come on!
Hang on, Bala!
Hang on!
Take this, brother!
-My Bey!
-Osman Bey!
My Bey!
My Bey! My Bey!
We came here for Geyhatu!
Save your rage for him, Osman Bey!
Come on!
Hang on, brother!
I am.
Alps!
Hold the Vizier!
I am going after Geyhatu.
Come on!
Konur...
...go after Osman.
Bring him to me.
Alive or dead.
Come on!
As you order!
Argus! Argus!
I can't let my soldiers die for nothing
in a hell like this!
Retreat!
-Do you hear me?
-Yes, Sir!
Soldier!
Retreat!
You came in time, Erbey.
I came a long way to here from Konya,
my Vizier.
What is my duty?
Konur.
Konur?
I believe he did the worst wrong, Erbey.
I think he offered his loyalty to Osman...
...and not the State.
Go after him, at once.
Konur has been my brother for a long
time.
But there is a price for betrayal!
The moment I see him do something
wrong I will bring you his head.
Attack!
Capture them all!
Come on!
Geyhatu!
I am angry like a wolf running after
its prey!
Geyhatu!
You have nowhere to go!
Come on!
Commander Geyhatu!
Thank God we could leave.
I will live because I will kill!
You are bleeding, Commander Geyhatu!
I will bandage your wound.
The guards will catch up.
Take it out.
Cerkutay!
Brother!
Your Osman Bey turned his back and left.
He left you to my mercy.
Prepare the logs.
Come on!
Your cruelty...
...is looming, Vizier Alemşah!
You could at least let out wounded
brother go!
Vizier!
No need.
You will die sooner or later.
When Osman finds out that I have you...
...then it will be your end.
Take these rebel men.
Threw them where they deserve
as they deserve.
Come on!
Cerkutay!
Slow down!
He is near.
He is near, Turgut Bey.
Come on!
Geyhatu!
Stop!
Let us finish our unfinished business!
Osman!
If it was easy to kill me...
...I wouldn't live this long, Osman!
Let's go, Commander Geyhatu.
Mother! I can't take it anymore!
Be patient, my girl.
It will be fine.
You are a strong hatun.
You can handle this.
Come on!
Hang on! Hang on!
Hang on!
Come on.
It will be hard.
Too hard.
Don't say!
She needs strength.
Go to the healing room.
Tell the midwife to prepare sherbet.
She knows what to do.
Come on, my girl.
I am taking care of it.
Mother!
If I could wait a little more...
...my Osman would be here too.
My Osman will come.
You will hold your child together, I hope.
He will.
Our baby will be born safely.
Right, mother?
Of course, my girl!
It wants to come to you.
So it will.
But obviously, it will be stubborn like
its father.
My Bey!
Brothers, come on!
Cerkutay!
Brother!
Hang on, my brother!
Hang on!
Hang on, brother!
Tunahan, hold it tight!
He can't carry heavy.
Hang on, my brother!
Come on, brothers!
Carry on!
You are good!
Let me go!
Brother!
Cerkutay!
Hang on! Hang on!
Brother!
My brother!
-Cerkutay!
-Hang on, brother!
Come on!
Calm down!
Vizier, at least let my brother go!
All of you deserve the same!
First the pit, then the hell!
Stop!
Have you no mercy?
I will carry my brother!
Let go!
Come here, brother.
Come here.
Hang on, Cerkutay.
Come here, brother.
Don't push!
Have you no mercy?
Come on!
Brothers!
Take Cerkutay!
Come here, brother.
Come on!
You will be fine, Cerkutay!
Konya saved the ones who...
...disobeyed the Vizier of Konya.
But now, there's no one to save them.
They are rebellious dogs!
Give the dogs raw meat and dirty water!
Bring the soldiers in Söğüt to Kayı
Tribe.
From now on, no one who loves
Osman...
...will be free.
Neither his mom, his hatuns or his child!
Clear!
As you order, my Vizier.
Alemşah!
Don't you dare touch the tribe!
Don't you dare touch the hatuns!
Stay away from our tribe!
Deh!
Delikız!
Brother!
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Thank you, brothers!
Geyhatu...
...clearly filled the road with traps.
But he can't stop us.
Now, we will be careful too.
Now we are sure, Osman Bey.
...since we face these traps...
...we are on the right way.
Come on.
Give me your hand!
Mother.
My pain is gone.
My baby?
Don't worry now.
It comes and goes.
Look, here is your baby.
Tell me when it moves.
All right.
Her water broke down early.
There was time.
Mother says the baby is there.
It doesn't seem to be easy, Malhun Hatun.
May my Allah give her strength,
make it easier.
I hope.
Don't let Bala Hatun hear.
She will be scared.
You are right.
Nothing will happen, right?
No, my girl. You just pray.
Take deep breaths.
Come on.
Think of the good, all right?
Her water broke down but...
Mother?
Is my baby fine?
It is fine, my girl.
Zehra!
Calm down, Bala.
Calm down.
Let's make her move a bit, right?
Sure, mother.
Come on!
Come on, my Bala. Hold onto me.
Wait.
Hold on to me, Bala.
What is this?
Oh, my Allah!
May you protect us!
Ayşe, Malhun go check outside.
Come on.
Mother...
...can it be Osman?
We will see, my girl.
What is going on here, Vizier Alemşah?
Aren't you going to welcome the Vizier of
Konya, Malhun Hatun?
Why are you drawing your swords
at my alps, Vizier?
What do you want from us?
Your alps are rebels like you.
They don't listen to
the Vizier of the State of Seljuk.
But today, I didn't come for them.
I came for you.
I arrest you, Bala Hatun and
Selcen Hatun...
...for helping Osman, who rebelled againts
the Seljuk State!
Let our hatuns go!
You can't take them!
What are you saying, Alemşah?
What is this?
Back off!
There is a birth happening inside.
Let my mother and Bala go.
I will come with you.
I no longer believe your games,
Malhun Hatun!
Get out of my way!
Let me go!
Go away! Let our hatuns go!
Leave, you dogs!
Aygül!
I am so sorry.
Deeply sorry.
Rogatus...
...died.
When Vizier attacked him with
his soldiers...
...it got even worse.
No one could get out of there.
As you will understand...
...I made a move and retreated to save
my soldiers.
You left him alone on the battlefield!
We couldn't even see who hit who!,
You left your brother alone
on the battlefield!
What could I do?
Should I have let my soldiers die?
You broke your promise, Nikola!
I made this alliance to protect my family
and my soldiers!
Not to die for nothing!
Also...
...Gündüz Bey...
...didn't you turn your back on your
brother for the same reason?
Gündüz Bey!
Vizier and Geyhatu know you are with us.
There is no turning back now.
Don't ever make a mistake.
Then my sword won't hit your sword.
It will hit your neck, Nikola!
Your neck!
Don't worry, Nikola.
I am saving you for myself.
Kosses...
...you are saving me for yourself, huh?
Argus!
I am Aya Nikola.
I'm never on the losing side.
Send the Vizier a messenger to tell him I
want to make up with him.
As you order, Sir.
I have crucially important things to tell
him.
Gündüz Bey!
I told Turgut too, that I know...
...when he will betray us.
He will, because he is afraid.
I don't know what you know,
Kosses.
But there is something I know.
Osman was never to work with us.
Pull yourself together, Gündüz Bey!
I have been with Osman in Konya and
Söğüt.
Choose your words wisely!
It is not the time to choose words!
It is time to know who is with you.
Because you don't look for the reason
of the betrayal.
You only punish.
Turks!
Stop! Don't you have any manners?
I told you, the woman is pregnant!
Shut up!
Soldiers!
Malhun Hatun, drop your sword!
Selcen Hatun, Bala Hatun!
Come here nicely!
Or I won't fear spilling any blood!
I am out of my patience!
You and that rebel Osman will be punished.
Don't you understand a word we are saying?
Why did you come again, devil?
I came to arrest you, Selcen Hatun.
What did we do that you are arresting us?
You ask as if you don't know, old woman.
You help your rebel son and
betray the state of Seljuk.
Here she is.
You can't stop lying, can you?
You told me the hatun was giving birth.
She is here in front of me.
Don't confuse us with yourself.
There is no lying about this.
The birth started, we make her walk so--
Shut up!
I believe what I see.
She can hang on until Söğüt like this.
Soldiers!
Tie them all!
Let us come and let Bala Hatun stay.
Malhun is right.
She can't walk.
The birth started.
We will come with you.
Hurry up, tie them all!
Come on!
Get off of me!
What kind of a man are you?
I can't even call you human!
Calling you an animal is an
insult to animals!
What are you, huh?
This is the end, Hatuns.
Brother!
Are you alright?
I'm, my bey.
Because of these traps, we can't
catch Geyhatu.
We'll destroy all his traps, my bey.
He is wounded. That's why
he is taking the easy road.
We'll take the high hills and
cliffs.
You'll go right.
We'll go left.
-We'll come Geyhatu's way.
-Alright, my bey.
But there are many caves
around here.
He might come after us instead.
Boran will go over the high ground.
We'll check every hole down here.
As you order, my bey.
May Allah bless our jihad.
Come on.
Thank you, brother.
Aygül.
Move! Move!
Ayşe Hatun...
what's happening?
-Don't even ask, Aygül.
The vizier.
-He is arresting my mother, Malhun, Bala.
-What are you saying?
-Bala, the baby! Isn't she giving birth?
-Yes, but he isn't listening.
He'll take them to Söğüt.
What?
-I'll show them!
-Stop! Come! Wait.
He has surrounded the tribe
with soldiers.
Go and inform Gündüz and Osman Bey.
We can't help them alone.
But maybe Gündüz can convince
the vizier.
Go to Harmankaya.
Harmankaya.
Gündüz was going there.
Get there in time, Aygül.
Bala can't take all that road
in this condition.
Alright, Ayşe Hatun.
Be careful.
-Keep your eyes open.
-Be careful.
What's your name?
Where are you going, woman?
Get out of my and save me the trouble.
Are you from the rebellious
Osman's family?
Thank you, Ayşe.
Come on.
Kayı Tribe!
What I do shouldn't be regarded
as tyranny.
My only wish is the good of
your tribe.
These women were helping the
rebel named Osman.
For that reason, they'll be trialed.
Mother Selcan is the mother
of the Kayı Tribe!
Bala Hatun is pregnant!
We'll protect the precious of Osman bey!
Let him go!
Don't touch them!
We are coming as you want.
An insult against me is an insult
against Sultan Mesut.
Revolting to the state has only one
punishment.
Traitors!
Vizier, I hope you get strangled.
You'll carry the blood of
the innocent on your hands forever.
You will answer for this, vizier.
You'll answer for every innocent
you killed.
Come on.
Kayı Tribe, look what this damned
man does.
See it and understand how
right Osman Bey was.
Let our ladies go!
Am I allowed? Orhan is so little.
He shouldn't get cold.
Aygül went to inform.
May Allah help you.
Thank you, Ayşe Hatun.
Retreat the soldiers at the tribe.
I have all his family.
I'll find Gündüz too, wherever
he is.
The cart will slow us down.
We'll go ahead.
Be careful.
I don't want any mistakes.
I'm alright.
Harmankaya Castle
Mari.
Aygül.
Are you alright?
What happened?
How's everyone?
Bad things happened, Mari.
That snake vizier raided the tribe.
He took the ladies.
Dishonorable vizier.
He doesn't think.
I'll take his brain out!
I need to talk to Gündüz Bey.
I heard that he is here.
He and my brother left.
Where, Mari?
We don't have time.
I don't know!
They left suddenly.
Aygül, I want to help!
Mari, look.
Bala Hatun, Malhun Hatun, Mother Selcan,
you are my family.
Mari, you are pregnant.
You must protect your baby.
Alright?
What will you do?
I can't lose time by looking
for Gündüz Bey.
I'll find Osman Bey.
Ready the soldiers.
We are leaving.
As you order.
-But, my lady--
-We are leaving, Cornelia!
I'll do anything for my family.
My child will learn to fight for
its family first.
You will be fine, brother.
You will be fine.
You are fine, brother.
You are fine.
Look here!
Aren't you humans?
Give us clean water!
What are you looking at?
This won't do.
We have to leave here.
Brothers. Lift me to the cage when
it gets dark.
After surviving to the night,
we'll find a way.
Cerkutay.
Hold yourself together.
Hang on, Cerkutay.
Hang on!
Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
Brother!
Pull yourself together!
Cerkutay!
Cerkutay can't die!
Brother!
Dishonorable!
Give us clean water!
Brother!
Cerkutay!
Cerkutay, open your eyes!
Follow these tracks.
I'll wait here.
The vizier was right.
You are up to something, Konur.
Damn it.
Alps...
Osman...
Where are you, Osman?
I'm here, Turgut Bey!
Get up!
Come on, brother.
-Boran!
-Konur!
Konur!
We were separated, brother.
We are together, brother.
I'm here, thank Allah.
Thank Allah.
Are you alright?
We are, my bey.
No matter how good he is, a weasel
can't kill a wolf.
Right, brother?
Yes, Turgut Bey.
Yes.
The vizier sent me, my bey.
I got rid of the soldiers.
I don't have my alps with me.
The vizier must have them.
We won't leave my brothers to them.
I didn't know, my bey. I went after
you into the forest.
You are working with Osman, Konur.
You turn your back to Konya and
be loyal to a bey.
We don't know what that vizier
is up to.
Spend some time in the forest
and return to him.
Say that you couldn't find us.
We won't return before taking
Geyhatu's life.
As you order, my bey.
Come on, brother.
Come on.
My child.
Our child is coming.
Where are you, Osman?
Bala, are you alright?
I'm feeling some pain.
It feels like my inside is crushed
as this cart swings.
Slow! Slow!
The woman is pregnant!
She is giving birth.
Aren't you afraid of Allah?
Stop and let us give her
a drop of water.
Give them water.
Give it to me.
Bala, drink it slowly.
Slowly, slowly.
Is it good?
Malhun.
This won't do, my daughter.
The baby is coming.
We must do something.
Bala!
Rogatus Lasgaris.
He fought for Bilecik all his life.
And he died when he was fighting
for the people of Bilecik.
His soul must be in peace.
What about you, Gündüz Bey?
Are you still judging us over Nikola?
We are fighting alongside you...
and dying alongside you.
Thank you, Kosses.
Thank you.
Wait.
Bamsı Bey's swords.
Bamsı Bey?
Ah, Cerkutay!
Ah!
My Allah, protect them!
My bey!
Gündüz Bey!
My warrior!
Are you alright?
I'm fine but...
the vizier took all the alps.
Alps!
Take our brother to the
brother! Go!
Osman Bey. Do you think the vizier
have him?
I don't think so.
If he had captured Osman...
he would announce it to the
whole world.
Osman must be after Geyhatu.
Return to your castle, Kosses.
I'll keep searching for Osman Bey.
Stop there, Gündüz Bey.
We'll go together to search for Osman.
Mari!
Mother!
We called you our sister for a reason!
Cornelia, hold Orhan.
Come.
Slowly!
Come on.
Hang on!
Come.
Mother!
Bala!
Come on, my girl.
Come on.
Keşik.
Were they protecting Genghis like this?
Why did none of the warriors
return?
Because they were trained to die,
not to return.
This is why.
And they died.
Now, I'll personally fight.
This cave will be Osman's grave!
Hang on! Hang on!
Hang on!
We can't go like this.
It begins.
Come on!
Bala! Hang on a little longer!
My Allah!
Protect my child!
Alps!
My bey.
Be careful.
Alright, my bey.
Look at this.
They are setting traps.
But this can only slow us.
We won't give up.
A little bit more, brothers.
The traps don't look old.
We are close.
We are.
As close as their breath.
It's better to be cautious.
Alright, my bey.
Come on.
Dogs are trying to eat the cage!
The vizier said that the captives
wouldn't sit silently.
He was right.
What good comes from being right
if you aren't the right person?
We are fighting for Allah's words.
What's your purpose?
They are just serving the vizier.
Keep seeing us as rebels.
We won't step back.
As you have this cage...
you can't do anything.
Go and get your last sleep.
Allah is great.
So, Nikola wants to build an
alliance with me again.
Lord Nikola wants to stand with power.
We aren't desperate to hold onto
desperate situations.
Those who see their graves ready,
want to stand with us.
Holes are dangerous for anyone who
don't see what's in front of them.
Your alliance with my lord Nikola
will give you power.
Think about it, my vizier.
Let's think about it.
I don't need to be allies with Nikola.
Konur.
You can leave, Konur.
Now, go to Osman...
and tell him that we are enemies
with Nikola.
You were right to be suspicious,
my vizier.
Konur got rid of the soldiers first...
and then he fought alongside Osman.
He is loyal to Osman.
I should behead him and send
his skull to Konya.
But I'll use him more smartly.
He should stay loyal to Osman.
Disloyal dog!
And you say that you couldn't
find Osman, huh?
Anyway. Anyway.
May I enter, my vizier?
Come in.
My vizier, ladies escaped on their
way to here.
Harmankaya soldiers attacked.
Erbey!
Yes, my vizier.
Get some soldiers...
and this idiot.
See where they ran into.
Search everywhere!
Bring them to me!
Consider it done, my vizier.
Come on!
Come here, it's good here.
Get here.
We are here, Bala.
We are here. Slowly.
Come.
Sit slowly. Come on.
Hang on, Bala!
It'll all be over.
It'll all be over!
Hang on, Bala!
Just a little bit more, Bala!
Hang on.
Hang on, Bala!
Alright.
Bala...
Drink this.
Drink some water.
Drink it.
Mari, we'll set fire.
We need to boil water.
Go and gather some sticks
or something!
Alright.
Hang on!
Come on!
Malhun.
We need cloth.
Hold this.
Yes, mother.
Hold on.
Mother, what's the situation?
She hanged on good.
She is too tired.
I'm afraid.
May Allah protect her and the baby.
Inshallah, mother.
Inshallah.
The traps stopped Osman.
The traps won't stop Osman.
It'll be my bloody hands,
Mingiyan.
I'll kill him!
When Temuçin(Genghis Khan) lost his
father...
his tribe didn't want him.
He was little.
They banished him.
They took his herd, his property.
Most importantly...
they took his sword.
Onon River fed Temuçin.
The mountains raised him.
He set traps for his enemies.
He destroyed the ones who
despised him.
Sky Tengri blessed him!
With the blessing,
he got stronger.
He didn't have a horse.
He tamed a deer!
He didn't have a sword.
He sculpted a stone!
He didn't have a bow.
He bent a branch!
But he didn't give up.
He lived...
and he brought death to those
who stood against him.
They thought Temuçin was just a child.
He received the blessing of Tengri.
He became Genghis Khan!
I have that blessing!
I do! I do! I do!
I will live and bring death upon
my enemies!
Hang on, my daughter.
Hang on, Bala!
Come on, hang on a little longer!
I'm powerless, mother.
Hang on, Bala.
Hang on!
You are a strong woman.
Come on.
Malhun.
Go and check Orhan.
Osman...
Where are you, Osman?
Bala, hang on.
Go to Bala.
Where are you?
Aygül will inform Osman Bey.
Hang on!
Bala.
Listen to me well now.
You waited a long time for
your child.
But the child has little time.
You will push for one last time,
with all your power.
Come on, one last time.
With the name of Allah!
Come on!
Come on, my pretty girl!
With all your power!
Come on, Bala!
With the name of Allah!
Mashallah, Bala!
It's coming!
My bey.
We need to set a fire and
burn this wound.
This will be worse.
We are in the dark.
If we set fire, we'll
be seen.
Alright, my bey.
You talked about fire.
And here it is, Boran.
If it's destiny, it'll come
with or without the fire.
Now, we'll burn them.
Ya Allah!
Baby?
Mother Selcan?
Mother?
My baby...
Mother...
Why isn't it crying?
-Mother?
-Say something!
Why isn't my baby crying?
Mother, say something!
Alright.
Mother, why isn't my baby crying?
Malhun! What will I do?
No! No!
What will I do?
No! No! Mother!
Why isn't my baby crying?
Why not?
Come on, I beg you!
Come on!
Say something!
No! No!
My baby!
Come on, my precious one!
I beg you!
Come on!
My child! My child! No!
Thank Allah!
Is it a girl or a boy, Mother Selcan?
An evangel, Bala!
Thank Allah!
My child!
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah!
Did you learn to fight like this
in Karabağ, Gencebey?
Aren't we all the same, Turgut Bey?
We all fight good.
Good job, brother.
We all fight against the tyrants.
This is what unites us.
Now...
come on.
Search everywhere!
Come on!
Osman...
I've seen many cities and villages burn.
I burnt most of them.
I burnt them!
I did!
I've seen many corpses.
I killed most of them!
I did it!
Hundreds of calamities happened.
I did all of them!
Your tribe will only be one
of them, Osman.
Just one of them.
I'll get into your tribe like
Genghis' burning birds.
I will! I will!
I will!
Even the land will burn!
The sky won't cry to put out this fire!
Your lineage won't even have a
grave, Osman!
Your children, your women, your men...
I will kill all of them!
Blood...
their blood will flow like a river.
It will join the land and reach
Erlik Khan!
It'll reach Erlik Khan!
As you get removed from History...
Geyhatu will live forever!
Say it, mother.
Anything you say.
I don't want anything but your child's
health.
Thank Allah for these beautiful days.
We have a son to grow
our lineage.
Thank Allh.
Orhan has a brother to fight
shoulder to shoulder.
Thank Allah many times!
My son.
Is this real, mother?
May Allah protect you.
Amin.
May Allah give him a long and
good life.
They'll be together with his brother
forever.
Inshallah, my daughter.
Inshallah.
This is a miracle.
Yes.
This is a miracle from the creator.
Inshallah your turn is next.
Bala!
Where are you, Osman?
Where are you?
My mighty Allah!
I'm grateful.
I'm most grateful.
We've never stopped counting on you.
We never will.
My Allah.
You illuminate our nights.
My Allah, we find salvation
in your mercy.
It is our cure.
My Allah.
For your holy cause...
to swing the Islam flag in the world...
give us strenght.
-Amin.
My Allah, you protect us from the
obstacles on our way.
-Amin.
Amin.
Bala.
My child.
My Allah.
My Allah, I hope my dream meant
something good.
My children.
My Allah.
You give us salvation.
Every hole will be searched.
We won't return before finding
them.
Come on.
Clean it, Saltuk.
Cerkutay.
Cerkutay. Brother.
Come on.
I'm alright, brothers.
I'm alright.
Cerkutay won't lose to those dogs.
And Cerkutay...
doesn't die.
Doesn't die.
He doesn't die.
We are fighting for the ummah...
and look what they are doing!
But our bey won't leave us here.
Yes!
They think that they imprisoned us
with that cage.
There isn't a cage where they can
put our hearts in.
Right?
A brave heart can't be captured.
It can't.
We'll leave here.
We will.
Inshallah, brother.
With Allah's approval...
we'll leave here.
We will, inshallah.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
The dog is here.
The destiny of rebels is this.
You are lower than animals.
By following Osman...
you are rebelling against
the Seljuk Vizier!
Call your Osman Bey for help now!
You are the one who is lower!
We'll leave here.
Of course, you will.
I'm here to let you out.
Now, it's time.
You will leave here and be food
for weasels.
You caught me, Osman.
You ruled with tyranny.
You became a tyrant.
The shoes of your horses razed
the lands!
You killed the innocent!
Now...
now it's time.
You caught me.
But you are late.
I'm already at my destination.
This is your hell.
Geyhatu.
With Allah's name!
We shouldn't get far, my lady.
Bala needs to eat, Cornelia.
She is weak.
The traces go this way.
There are caves ahead.
They must be there.
They can't go far with the pregnant
woman.
Come on.
I'm here, brother!
I'm here, my bey!
Shoot!
Osman Bey!
We must go!
What are you saying, brother?
I've been waiting for this moment!
Why should I stop?
Osman Bey!
He has our alps!
The vizier raided the tribe.
He has the ladies.
What are you saying?
I'll get Mingiyan from Osman's hands.
He knows a lot.
I need him!
Where are the twenty thousand warriors?
Commander Geyhatu.
They are almost here.
They should.
They should bring doom to these
lands!
My bey.
I left to find Gündüz Bey.
Then, I went to Söğüt to find
them.
Thank Allah, they escaped.
Thank Allah.
Then I found Gündüz Bey on the
road and we came to you.
Thank you.
We must to find them.
The vizier has the alps.
We'll save the alps.
We'll take the ladies.
If it's our last resort.
I'll arm the remaining alps
and women.
I'll inform all the
friendly beys.
Do you give permission?
Thank you.
Send messengers.
Arm everyone who can hold
a sword.
Everyone should be ready.
It's heating up.
As you order, my bey.
I'll go to the ladies.
Alps don't need soldiers.
This will suffice.
Come here.
Geyhatu's secretive.
He knows everything about the Mongols.
Mingiyan will rule these lands...
when Geyhatu leaves here.
But now, he is in our hands.
Turgut Bey.
Go to our alps with him.
-Kosses.
-Osman Bey.
Return to your castle.
Brother.
Go to the tribe with Aygül.
The tribe is under your care.
Come on.
My bey.
I couldn't say it but...
Bala Hatun...
she was giving birth.
My Allah, help us.
Help us, my Allah!
Mari.
The Vizier's soldiers are in the forest.
They are coming closer.
My Allah, help us.
What are you doing?
Wait.
I'm alright, mother.
No.
You need to gather your strenght.
Sit.
Malhun.
Give her Orhan.
Mother is right.
With the name of Allah.
Come on now.
Mother, be careful.
Alaca!
What are you doing here?
Bala?
Come on!
A stranger is approaching!
Where is Osman Bey?
What's the difference, Vizier Alemşah?
My bey?
Turgut Bey!
Aren't you going to behead us all?
I will. You, Osman, the beys
you gathered at the council...
I'll behead you all.
Would one revolt before giving up
on his life?
Now, listen to me well.
You will give our alps to me.
And I'll give you what you want.
Good job, Turgut Bey.
I don't want anything but your life.
But tell me what it is.
Power. You like power, Vizier Alemşah.
You want power.
Here it is.
Mingiyan!
The secretive of the Mongols.
Geyhatu's trusted general to rule
these lands.
Mingiyan.
Turgut Bey brought Mingiyan.
I know.
Geyhatu is alive.
But we aren't afraid of him.
You are.
If he hears that you had an opportunity
to save Mingiyan but you refused it...
then, I pity you,
Alemşah the brave.
Commander.
It looks like a cave entrance.
Step back!
Don't come any closer!
Don't hamper!
Surrender!
We'll fight until we die!
But we won't surrender.
Alaca?
Alaca.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
I'm here, mother!
-Son!
-Osman!
I'm here, mother!
My bey!
My Allah, protect us.
Osman! Osman!
Thank Allah!
I've been waiting to say this
for a long time.
You have another son, Osman Bey!
Mashallah!
Take him.
Is this a dream, Osman?
I'm afraid to close my eyes.
This is an evangel!
This is an answer to our prayers!
You've come with luck.
My son.
My Orhan.
Give him to me.
Here.
With the name of Allah.
Orhan.
My son.
Look.
Look at your brother.
Mother.
Malhun.
If...
you allow it...
I want to name him Alaeddin.
Sure.
Let's return to our home now.
With the name of Allah.
Allahu Akbar.
I bear witness that there is no god
but Allah...
and that Muhammad (PBUH) is the servant
and Messenger of Allah.
Hurry to the prayer. Hurry to the prayer.
Hurry to salvation. Hurry to salvation.
Allahu Akbar.
There is no god except the One God.
I bear witness that there is no god
except for the One God.
I bear witness that Muhammad is
the messenger of God.
Hurry to the prayer. Hurry to the prayer.
Hurry to salvation. Hurry to salvation.
Kad Kâmeti's Salâh.
Allahu Akbar.
There is no god except the One God.
Your name is Alaeddin Ali.
Osman Bey's son, Alaeddin Ali.
May Allah make you one of his
good subjects.
Amin.
-May you always be on the right path.
-Amin.
Amin.
May Allah keep your feet on
the right path.
Amin.
May the great state that your father
will found...
grow and prosper with you.
Amin.
With the name of Allah.
Amin, my sheik.
Amin.
May Allah keep you with us.
Alaeddin Ali.
Mashallah.
With the name of Allah.
My sheik.
-Boran.
-My bey.
Play your kopuz.
As you order, my bey.
There are always troubles.
Some people are brave.
A hundred Moses stands against
modern pharaohs!
Against the modern Nimrods,
many Abrahams stand firmly!
All around the world, in the
dungeons of the tyrant...
on horseback for days,
for independence!
Turk means hope for the world.
When the laws order, arrows
know their destination.
When the Turks get to the battlefield,
it's the endgame.
the tyrants are helpless.
All the evil traps get useless.
Allah helps the Turks,
the nightmare of the tyrants.
When the Turks charge,
the enemy loses formation.
My Allah, you give strenght
to our army.
Give the world to the Turks
to form Turan.
Make our just state the head
of the world.
They found many states,
the armies of wolf banners.
The enemies of the Turks will
answer to Allah.
The enemies of Islam will
They found many states,
the armies of wolf banners.
The enemies of the Turks will
answer to Allah.
The enemies of Islam will
-Mashallah.
-Well done, brother.
Thank you, my bey.
Thank you.
Osman.
Think that you saved your women.
Think that you slipped out
of my hand.
Neither you nor your people...
your children,
even a sheep from your tribe...
will survive.
Erbey, prepare the armies.
We'll spill a lot of blood.
As you order, my vizier.
Now, I'll end this for good.
The great sycamore that I've
seen in my dream...
is growing every day.
My children...
Orhan...
and Alaeddin.
You...
are the roots of this great sycamore.
A state with such roots,
will rule the whole world...
to bring order.
The flag of Islam...
will be carried by you.
Ride your horses forward.
The lands your horses step on
will prosper.
Where your swords reach
will be the house of justice.
My children...
don't return before waving the
flag of the Turks.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com